<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">
	<ui:style>
	
	.HTMLheader{
		padding-top:50px
	}
	</ui:style>
	<g:HTMLPanel addStyleNames='{style.HTMLheader}'>
		
	
		<!-- PANELE INICIO-->
        <div class="row" >
            <div class="col-lg-12 col-md-12 col-sm-12 col-xs-12">
                <div class="panel ">

                    <!--Titulo-->
                    <div class="panel-heading">
                        <h3 class="panel-title">
                            <a class="accordion-toggle" data-toggle="collapse" data-parent="#accordion" href="#collapse1">
                                  What do we do?
                            </a>
                        </h3>
                    </div>

                    <!--Texto-->
                    <div id="collapse1" class="panel-collapse collapse in">
                        <div class="panel-body">
                            <div class="panel-text"  align="justify">

                                <p>
                                Today there are various techniques of multi-objective optimization study areas regarding Operations Research. However, in most of these it is considered as a guide base for the analysis of Pareto fronts with certain characteristics and typically require a starting point for starting your searches. Some of this lonely ABLE son of one solution: give for each execution. On the other hand there are areas of research Newest revolving around metrics and population dynamics that deliver evolutionary algorithms, is here Where Wanted: deliver capable of generating a graphical representation of the solutions or Pareto fronts Tool, delivered by algorithms and metrics to facilitate study campaign performance.
: In addition to the above, in the current project seeks to develop a robust and scalable tool that allows a future incorporate features that belong to the area of ​​operations and generate academic community.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>

                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
        
        
        
        <!-- UPLOAD -->
        <div class="row" >
            <div class="col-lg-12 col-md-12 col-sm-12 col-xs-12">
                <div class="panel ">

                    <!--Titulo-->
                    <div class="panel-heading">
                        <h3 class="panel-title">
                            <a class="accordion-toggle" data-toggle="collapse" data-parent="#accordion" href="#collapse2">
                                  How to Create a File?
                            </a>
                        </h3>
                    </div>

                    <!--Texto-->
                    <div id="collapse2" class="panel-collapse collapse ">
                        <div class="panel-body">
                            <div class="panel-text"  align="justify">

                                <p>
                                	Hi, the first that you need is get a text file with the result obtained from an algorithm of aproximation that gives you the pareto front coordenates. 
                                	The second thing is go to FILES and create this file, please verify that the coordenates format be exacly as the example in HELP option. Fill all the fields and paste de results.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>

                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
        
        <!-- PLOT-->
        <div class="row" >
            <div class="col-lg-12 col-md-12 col-sm-12 col-xs-12">
                <div class="panel ">

                    <!--Titulo-->
                    <div class="panel-heading">
                        <h3 class="panel-title">
                            <a class="accordion-toggle" data-toggle="collapse" data-parent="#accordion" href="#collapse3">
                                  How to plot a file?
                            </a>
                        </h3>
                    </div>

                    <!--Texto-->
                    <div id="collapse3" class="panel-collapse collapse ">
                        <div class="panel-body">
                            <div class="panel-text"  align="justify">

                                <p>
                                	After Create the file select the file from your list of files and send it to PLOT clicking "Add to Plot". the next part is go to TOOLS then select PLOT.
                                	Inside PLOT depends on what do you want to do inside the plot, after you deside just click in "plot" button. Well that's all Folks!!
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>

                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
        
        <!-- METRICS -->
        <div class="row">
            <div class="col-lg-12 col-md-12 col-sm-12 col-xs-12">
                <div class="panel ">

                    <!--Titulo-->
                    <div class="panel-heading">
                        <h3 class="panel-title">
                            <a class="accordion-toggle" data-toggle="collapse" data-parent="#accordion" href="#collapse4">
                                  What are the metrics?
                            </a>
                        </h3>
                    </div>

                    <!--Texto-->
                    <div id="collapse4" class="panel-collapse collapse ">
                        <div class="panel-body">
                            <div class="panel-text" align="justify">
                               
                                <h5>Entropy</h5> 
                                <p>Resume
                                </p>  
                                                              
                                <h5>Spacing</h5>  
                                <p>Resume
                                </p>
                                                              
                                <h5>Error ratio</h5>  
                                <p>Resume
                                </p> 
                                                             
                                <h5>Generational Distance</h5>  
                                <p>Resume
                                </p>  
                                                            
                                <h5>Cover</h5>  
                                <p>Resume
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>

                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
        
        <!-- METRICS -->
        <div class="row">
            <div class="col-lg-12 col-md-12 col-sm-12 col-xs-12">
                <div class="panel ">

                    <!--Titulo-->
                    <div class="panel-heading">
                        <h3 class="panel-title">
                            <a class="accordion-toggle" data-toggle="collapse" data-parent="#accordion" href="#collapse5">
                                  How to use the metrics?
                            </a>
                        </h3>
                    </div>

                    <!--Texto-->
                    <div id="collapse5" class="panel-collapse collapse ">
                        <div class="panel-body">
                            <div class="panel-text" align="justify">
                               
                                <p>
                                Hi, the first step is go to TOOLS menu, then select METRICS, inside metrics you will see the ones available in the system and the files you already have (if you don't see any go to FAQ 'How to upload a file'), the first thing you need to do is select the files you need to evaluate and after select the metric that you need. 
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>

                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
        
        <!-- Frameworks info -->
        <div class="row">
            <div class="col-lg-12 col-md-12 col-sm-12 col-xs-12">
                <div class="panel ">

                    <!--Titulo-->
                    <div class="panel-heading">
                        <h3 class="panel-title">
                            <a class="accordion-toggle" data-toggle="collapse" data-parent="#accordion" href="#collapse6">
                                  Frameworks that we use?
                            </a>
                        </h3>
                    </div>

                    <!--Texto-->
                    <div id="collapse6" class="panel-collapse collapse ">
                        <div class="panel-body">
                            <div class="panel-text"  align="justify">
                               
                                <h5>Google Web Toolkit</h5>    
                                <p>GWT is a development toolkit for building and optimizing complex browser-based applications. Its goal is to enable productive development of high-performance web applications without the developer having to be an expert in browser quirks, XMLHttpRequest, and JavaScript. GWT is used by many products at Google, including AdWords, AdSense, Flights, Hotel Finder, Offers, Wallet, Blogger. It’s open source, completely free, and used by thousands of developers around the world.
                                </p>
                                
                                <h5>Bootstrap</h5>    
                                <p>Bootstrap is a sleek, intuitive, and powerful, mobile first front-end framework for faster and easier web development. It uses HTML, CSS and Javascript. Bootstrap was developed by Mark Otto and Jacob Thornton at Twitter. It was released as an open source product in August 2011 on GitHub.
                                </p>
                            
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>

                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
        
        <!-- Frameworks info -->
        <div class="row">
            <div class="col-lg-12 col-md-12 col-sm-12 col-xs-12">
                <div class="panel ">

                    <!--Titulo-->
                    <div class="panel-heading">
                        <h3 class="panel-title">
                            <a class="accordion-toggle" data-toggle="collapse" data-parent="#accordion" href="#collapse7">
                                  Who i am?
                            </a>
                        </h3>
                    </div>

                    <!--Texto-->
                    <div id="collapse7" class="panel-collapse collapse ">
                        <div class="panel-body">
                            <div class="panel-text"  align="justify">
                                 
                                <p>Hi I'm Carlos Gutierrez Acevedo, thesis student at the Universidad Católica Santísima Concepción , Chile. The present system is my thesis project called "Web Application Analysis results multi objective optimization.", and my guide is the academic Pedro Gómez Meneses</p>
                                
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>

                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
	
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 